<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BaseApp</string>
    <!--刷新-->
    <string name="pull_down_refresh">Slide down to refresh</string>
    <string name="release_refresh">Release the refresh immediately</string>

    <string-array name="cash_tabs">
        <item>Income record</item>
        <item>Expenditure record</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="refreshing">Refresh</string>
    <string name="str_sign_in">Login</string>
    <string name="str_rd_home">Home</string>
    <string name="str_rd_order">USDT</string>
    <string name="str_rd_task">Status</string>
    <string name="str_rd_member">Upload</string>
    <string name="str_rd_mine">Mine</string>
    <string name="str_touxiao">Avatar</string>
    <string name="str_me_phone">Phone number</string>
    <string name="str_bank_info">Payment information</string>
    <string name="str_usdt">USDT</string>
    <string name="str_zhifupas">Withdrawals password</string>
    <string name="str_accout_blance">Account Balance</string>
    <string name="str_accout_blance_ex">Account Balance:</string>
    <string name="str_now_zhifu">Immediate payment</string>
    <string name="str_tixian">Withdraw money</string>
    <string name="str_chongzhi">Recharge</string>
    <string name="str_chongzhi_vip">Purchase upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_tixianjl">Withdrawal record</string>
    <string name="str_shouzhijl">Income and expenditure records</string>
    <string name="str_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="str_me_infos">Personal information</string>
    <string name="str_day_task_sum">Daily task：</string>
    <string name="str_invitcode_">Invitation code:</string>
    <string name="str_accout_blance_">Account Balance</string>
    <string name="str_now_dj">Current level</string>
    <string name="str_now_shenj">Upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_task_sumn_">Number of tasks</string>
    <string name="str_vip_info_">After upgrading \nyou can get more tasks</string>
    <string name="str_day_task_sum_1">Daily task num：</string>
    <string name="str_task_yonj">Single task bonus：</string>
    <string name="str_day_shouyi">Daily income：</string>
    <string name="str_baozhengjin">Cash pledge:</string>
    <string name="str_task_shili">View task examples</string>
    <string name="str_look_task_sl">Submit</string>
    <string name="str_start_task">Start task</string>
    <string name="str_start_task_1">Do it</string>
    <string name="str_no_data">Empty data</string>
    <string name="str_receive_order">Auto Process</string>
    <string name="str_copy_success">Copy Success</string>
    <string name="str_input_error">input error</string>
    <string name="str_tixian_pass">Withdrawals password</string>
    <string name="str_yuebuzu">Insufficient balance</string>
    <string name="str_pass_inut_tis">Passwords are inconsistent, please re-enter</string>
    <string name="str_save_1">Confirm</string>
    <string name="str_rd_team">Brokerage</string>
    <string name="str_mine_title_03">  Record  </string>
    <string name="str_bank_name">Bank Name</string>
    <string name="str_bank_name_1">Please click to select a bank</string>
    <string name="str_hime_login_1">Enter your phone number</string>
    <string name="str_him_login_2">Enter password</string>
    <string name="str_him_login_3">Invitation code(Optional)</string>
    <string name="str_him_login_4">SMS verification code</string>
    <string name="str_commt_task_pic">Screenshot of completed task</string>
    <string name="str_tos_login_2">invalid phone number</string>
    <string name="str_sure_commit">Confirm submission</string>
    <string name="str_dia_newuser1">Your level: </string>
    <string name="str_dia_newuser2">Congratulations on becoming VIP0! \n\nGot</string>
    <string name="str_dia_newuser3">\n\nGo to complete the tasks and get more cash rewards!</string>
    <string name="str_dia_newuser4">let\'s start</string>
    <string name="str_extr_0">Pending</string>
    <string name="str_extr_1">Success</string>
    <string name="str_extr_2">Failure</string>
    <string name="str_extr_4">Your withdrawal application has been received, and the finance is under review. The review time is within 24 hours to 48 hours. You can receive your withdrawal as soon as possible on the same day. If you do not receive it on the same day, please do not rush it.\n\nPlease be patient, this is often because there are too many people who initiate withdrawals, it takes time to process, or the payment channel is congested.\n\nIf the withdrawal fails, please contact customer service for consultation.</string>
    <string name="str_extr_5">Congratulations, your withdrawal has arrived!\n\nYou can share it with your friends. Please share a screenshot of your successful withdrawal in the NoiseMedia telegram group\n\nInvite more people to join NoiseMedia and have a chance to get rich rewards.</string>
    <string name="str_extr_6">The mobile phone number is inconsistent with the bank card binding, please fill in the correct bank card account number and bound mobile phone number.\n\nThe amount has been refunded to your platform account balance, you can view the refund record in the income and expenditure records.</string>
    <string name="str_extr_7">The bank account is not supported. Please change to a new bank account. Then reapply for withdrawal.\n\nThe amount will be refunded to your plaThe amount has been refunded to your platform account balance, you can view the refund record in the income and expenditure records.</string>
    <string name="str_extr_7_1">You do not meet the withdrawal rules, please check the detailed withdrawal rules. If the rules are met, the withdrawal is successful.\n\nThe amount has been refunded to your platform account balance, you can view the refund record in the income and expenditure records.</string>
    <string name="str_extr_8">Income and expenditure records</string>
    <string name="str_extr_9">ok</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_1">Upgrade failed</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_2">Your account balance is insufficient, please recharge.</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_3">Recharge now</string>
    <string name="str_vip_upgrade_1">Balance upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_vip_upgrade_2">VIP %1$s upgrade fee is Rs %2$s (Which will be debited directly from account balance)\nAt the same time, cash pledge is Cash pledge: %3$s SAR (In order to receive tasks, your balance needs to remain above %4$s SAR as a cash pledge)\n\nTherefore, before upgrading, please make sure that your balance is sufficient. After the upgrade is successful, you cannot downgrade.\n\nWhat does the Cash pledge mean?\nIf you upgrade to VIP1 or higher, it means that you have decided to cooperate with NoiseMedia, and you must deposit enough margin in the balance to maintain the cooperation with NoiseMedia.\nTherefore, the required balance is stored in your account as balance Balance Required. After you pay enough deposit according to the current VIP Balance Required, the member can immediately perform tasks according to their VIP level. Members can withdraw all balances at any time (including all the income you earn and the deposit you deposit).\nSome members have been upgraded to VIP by mistake and do not intend to deposit a full balance as a deposit. It is recommended that members invite more friends to earn referral bonuses until you earn enough income as a deposit. We would like to remind all members not to upgrade that if you are not prepared to deposit your money into the balance as a deposit, the membership fee will not be returned to your balance because the VIP level cannot be downgraded to a lower level.</string>
    <string name="str_vip_upgrade_4"> \n\nwhich will be deducted from your balance.\n\n Please make sure your account balance is sufficient.</string>
    <string name="str_vip_upgrade_3">Confirm upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_extr_success_1">Successful application</string>
    <string name="str_extr_success_2">Will be approved within 1 working day! \n\nYou can check the withdrawal status in the withdrawal record.</string>
    <string name="str_extr_success_3">Withdrawal record</string>
    <string name="str_login_sencsu">Send Success</string>
    <string name="str_order_ts_1">Prompt</string>
    <string name="str_order_ts_2">Does not match your current level.\n\nPlease go to the current level to receive the task</string>
    <string name="str_order_ts_3">Current level</string>
    <string name="str_new_u_order_ts_1">prompt</string>
    <string name="str_new_u_order_ts_2">Please complete at least %1$s novice tasks！</string>
    <string name="str_new_u_order_ts_3">Let\'s Start</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_411">Please enter your WhatsApp number</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_412">Please enter the USDT collection address</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_413">Enter the withdrawal amount</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_4_1">Please set the withdrawal password</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_5">Withdrawal rules:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_7_1">1. Minimum withdrawal: 200</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_8">2. The withdrawal time is from Monday to Sunday from 10 am to 10 pm.</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_9">3. After you submit the withdrawal application, your funds will arrive in your account within 24 hours. If you have not received the payment within the time limit, please contact customer service for assistance in time.</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_11">Amount:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_12">Address:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_13">WhatsApp:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_14">Mode:</string>
    <string name="str_pass_0">Please enter your current password</string>
    <string name="str_pass_1">Please enter your new password</string>
    <string name="str_pass2">Re-enter your new password</string>
    <string name="str_pass3">Confirm</string>
    <string name="str_pass4">Please enter a pure 6-digit number as the withdrawal password.</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_1">Your Name：</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_2">Please enter your name</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_3">Phone：</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_4">Please enter phone number</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_6">Payment methods：</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_7">Your Email：</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_8">Please enter your email</string>
    <string name="str_vip_rechar_1">Level amount：</string>
    <string name="str_update_1">Update Now</string>
    <string name="str_upsucce_1">Upgrade successed</string>
    <string name="str_upsucce_2">let\'s start</string>
    <string name="str_upsucce_3">Congratulations on your successful upgrade!\n\nYour current level is VIP</string>
    <string name="str_upsucce_4">\n\nYou can earn </string>
    <string name="str_upsucce_5">a day</string>
    <string name="str_pass_err">wrong password</string>
    <string name="str_you_won">You won</string>
    <string name="str_rupees">$!</string>
    <string name="str_information">Information</string>
    <string name="str_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="str_about_01">Starcom is a global media and communications agency that was founded in Chicago. The company provides a wide range of advertising and marketing services to clients, including media planning and buying, digital strategy, data and analytics, and content creation.</string>
    <string name="str_about_02" formatted="false">Starcom is the Human Experience Company. A world-renowned media communications agency, we harness the power of media, technology and data to create experiences people love and actions brands need. With more than 7,000 employees worldwide, Starcom partners with the world\'s leading marketers and new establishment brands, including Bank of America, Best Buy, Coca-Cola, Kellogg Company, KraftHeinz, Novartis, P/G, Samsung, Visa and more. Starcom is part of Publicis Media within Publicis Groupe [Euronext Paris FR0000130577, CAC40], one of the world’s leading communications groups.</string>
    <string name="str_about_03">We work with some of the world\'s most loved brands and leading startups to help them grow globally.</string>
    <string name="str_about_04">We combine data, technology and full funnel strategies to drive positive ROAS for our clients.</string>
    <string name="str_about_05">Our team of content creators, marketers, strategists and social gurus have developed some of the largest and most engaged communities on Instagram and Facebook and now we\'re helping brands make social media an essential channel for their company or their cause.</string>
    <string name="str_about_06">NoiseMedia is an intelligent money-making system developed in the UK. After a year of research and development and 4 months of internal testing, it was finally launched.</string>
    <string name="str_about_07">This product is dedicated to solving the problem of online marketers in terms of visitor growth on social networks. Accurate matching through intelligent systems can increase the number of users and exposure of related products, thereby increasing the popularity of related products. Finally, complete the sales increase goal. (Welcome online merchants and trading companies to cooperate with NoiseMedia)</string>
    <string name="str_about_08">At the same time, NoiseMedia can provide freelancers with long-term beneficial work, providing more job opportunities throughout the intelligent system. In our timed task system, when you complete the corresponding task, you will receive the merchant\'s commission.</string>
    <string name="str_about_09">The industrial logic of NoiseMedia comes from the following aspects;</string>
    <string name="str_about_10">1. The operation of the intelligent NoiseMedia system is only used to match orders and users, and the product itself does not participate in any promotions or commission settlements.</string>
    <string name="str_about_11">2. Traders should ensure that the tasks published by the platform are true and effective, and strictly abide by local laws and regulations. Including, but not limited to, no racial discrimination, no economic fraud, over 18, no political discrimination, no personal attack and other related inappropriate speech or behavior. The platform will carefully check the tasks and will not be held responsible for the results of the violations.</string>
    <string name="str_about_12">3. NoiseMedia\'s revenue comes from the merchant\'s task commission and the user\'s VIP purchase fee. If there are other tax-related issues, the tax department will investigate separately and announce the results of the investigation.</string>
    <string name="str_about_13">4. Members of the platform must perform the tasks displayed by the commission provider honestly and must not cheat or obtain illegal commissions by cheating. Once discovered, the consequences will be at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="str_about_14">5. This product is a centralized service platform, which may be closed due to force majeure factors such as pirate attacks, earthquakes, tsunamis, conventional or unconventional military operations at the location from the server. Downtime caused by any behavior does not represent the voluntary behavior of the platform, and the platform will resume normal services as soon as possible.</string>
    <string name="str_about_15">6. NoiseMedia has the right to update and modify the product. At the same time, NoiseMedia must notify all users 24 hours in advance of updates and revisions to laws and regulations.</string>
    <string name="str_news_001">Welcome to NoiseMedia!</string>
    <string name="str_news_002">Welcome to NoiseMedia. You can start your earning journey here.\n\nDear everyone,\n\n1 Register on NoiseMedia platform and get Rs 5.\n\n2 Regular employees can earn daily income by completing the media tasks of the platform.\n\n3 The income of the team will be unlimited, the team will be what you should pay attention to.\n\n4 NoiseMedia also offers fixed deposits of various tenors.\n\n5 Withdraw funds in seconds on our NoiseMedia platform.\n\n6 All agents who want to make more money can invite your subordinates to upgrade their membership.</string>
    <string name="str_news_003">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_news_004">Three-level team rewards!!</string>
    <string name="str_news_005">You can form your own team and let the team make more money for you! \n\nYou can get level 1 commission rewards for team upgrades and level 3 commission rewards for team tasks. \n\nThe more teams, the more you earn! !</string>
    <string name="str_news_006">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_messg_title">Detail</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_001">Upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_002">If you want to make more money every day, you can upgrade your level.</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_003">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_004">Team upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_005">Invite your team to upgrade, you can get 1 levels of commission rewards for team upgrades! \n\nAs long as your team is upgraded, you can make money every day!</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_006">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_mine_dialog_001">Become the boss!！</string>
    <string name="str_mine_dialog_002">You can invite friends to get invitation rewards, or you can invite friends to form a team.\n\nThe team can make money for you every day!\n\nThe more teams you have, the higher your team income!</string>
    <string name="str_mine_dialog_003">let\'s start!</string>
    <string name="str_share_take_money">Share Take Money</string>
    <string name="str_lose">LOSE !!</string>
    <string name="str_message_info">Information</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_112">Recharge</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_113">Do you want to recharge?\n\nTouch  \'Yes\' to  next step</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_114">Yes</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_115">No</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_116">Recharge Instructions:</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_117">1.NoiseMedia is a global media part-time task system. For the convenience of our global staff, we use the very secure channel cryptocurrency USDT trc20 and local payment systems for settlement.</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_118">2. The recharge system is an automatic system. Each customer will be assigned an exclusive recharge address. (You need to obtain a new address for each recharge). The time limit is half an hour. Please copy the address here to transfer within the valid time. After completing the transfer, you will receive your balance in about 5 minutes. If you do not receive it within the time limit, please contact customer service for assistance.</string>
    <string name="str_rechar_119">3. NoiseMedia will not ask for any private recharge, and no official staff will send you a private message to request transfer. Please pay attention to distinguish the true and false to protect the safety of your property.</string>
    <string name="str_caution_01">Upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_caution_03">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_financial_001">Successful withdrawal</string>
    <string name="str_financial_002">Funds have been withdrawn to your account balance</string>
    <string name="str_financial_003">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_financial_004">Less than the minimum deposit amount</string>
    <string name="str_financial_005">Insufficient balance, please recharge your account first</string>
    <string name="str_financial_006">Congratulations</string>
    <string name="str_financial_007">After expiration, you will be able to earn %1$s!</string>
    <string name="str_financial_008">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_financial_009">Investing</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0010">Withdrawal</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0011">complete</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0012">Total assets</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0013">Yesterday\'s interest</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0014">Total interest income</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0015">Product</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0016">My deposit</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0017">Minimum deposit</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0018">NoiseMedia fund</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0019">Caution money</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0020">Margin withdrawal time：</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0021">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_balance">Balance</string>
    <string name="str_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="str_no">No</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0023">Expected return：</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0024">Date of Expiry：</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0025">Deposit amount</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0026">Total revenue:</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0027">One Day：</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0028">Internet reta:+</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0029">NoiseMedia fund</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0030">You need to recharge to your account balance first, and then make a deposit. After the deposit expires, you can immediately withdraw the total income.</string>
    <string name="str_financial_0031">Got it</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_01">Amount:</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_02">Please enter the recharge amount</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_03">WhatsApp:</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_04">The minimum recharge amount is Rs 20</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_05">Please enter your WhatsApp number</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_08">USDT TRC-20 Wallet address</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_09">Copy Address</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_10">NoiseMedia requires that the recharge amount must be a multiple of 5, please enter the correct recharge amount.</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_11">Amount:</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_12">copy</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_16">I have completed the payment</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_17">After the transfer is successful, please contact the Recharge Service and send a screenshot of your transfer, which can speed up the confirmation process</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_18">Transfer description</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_19">1: The deposit address is valid for 30 minutes. Please complete the transfer within 30 minutes after obtaining the address. If it exceeds 30 minutes, please do not transfer to the expired address to avoid trouble.\n2: The recharge will be reflected in your account balance within 1\-5 minutes after you complete the transfer. If the recharge has not been received for a long time, please contact the online customer service for assistance.</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_20">Operation steps</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_21">1. Copy the address</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_22">2. Open a cryptocurrency wallet or exchange</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_23">3. Transfer USDT (TRC20)</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_24">4. Click [Complete Recharge].</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_01">title</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_02">buy</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_03">升级成功</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_04">立即购买</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_05">buy</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_06">Your Level:</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_07">tisp</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_08">ok</string>
    <string name="str_dialo_common_10">Type A</string>
    <string name="str_dialog_add_group_01">Contact service</string>
    <string name="str_dialog_add_group_02">Telegram group</string>
    <string name="str_dialog_add_group_03">Telegram CS</string>
    <string name="str_dialog_add_group_04">WhatsApp CS</string>
    <string name="str_dialog_add_group_05">WA Group</string>
    <string name="str_dialog_app_apk_update_01">New Version</string>
    <string name="str_dialog_app_apk_update_02">Download in the browser</string>
    <string name="str_frm_mine_01">Platform Rules</string>
    <string name="str_frm_mine_02">Customer care</string>
    <string name="str_frm_mine_03">FAQ</string>
    <string name="str_frm_mine_04">Notice</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_01">Copy</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_02">Invite new members</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_04">Copy Link</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_05">WhatsApp CS</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_06">Facebook</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_07">TG Group</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_08">Deposit</string>
    <string name="str_myteam01_09">Telegram</string>
    <string name="str_myteam02_02">Today\'s Referral\n Bonus</string>
    <string name="str_myteam02_03">Total Referral Bonus</string>
    <string name="str_myteam02_04">Today\'s team\n added</string>
    <string name="str_myteam02_05">Total team</string>
    <string name="str_myteam02_06">Team earnings\n today</string>
    <string name="str_myteam02_07">Total team earning</string>
    <string name="str_myteam02_08">(People)</string>
    <string name="str_myteam04_1">Number of\n first-level\n subordinates</string>
    <string name="str_myteam04_2">Number of\n secondary\n subordinates</string>
    <string name="str_myteam04_3">Number of\n third-level\n subordinates</string>
    <string name="str_myteam021_04">Reward</string>
    <string name="str_myteam04_01">  Rules  </string>
    <string name="str_banner_01">Notice</string>
    <string name="str_financicl_01">[Set] 180 days</string>
    <string name="str_financicl_02">Deposit</string>
    <string name="str_financicl_03">180 days</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_record_title">Recharge record</string>
    <string name="str_usdt_title">USDT Payment</string>
    <string name="str_amount_msg">Please enter amount</string>
    <string name="str_whatsapp_msg">Please enter your WhatsApp number</string>
    <string name="str_kenya_pay_msg">Please continue to complete the payment</string>
    <string name="str_minimum_recharge">Minimum recharge Rs 20</string>
    <string name="str_withdrawal_amount">Please enter the withdrawal amount</string>
    <string name="str_maxmum_deposit">Above the maximum deposit</string>
    <string name="str_app_correctly">Please use the application correctly</string>
    <string name="str_select_country">Please select your country</string>
    <string name="str_upgrade_vip">Please upgrade to %1$s first</string>
    <string name="str_no_open">The current level is not yet open, it will be open soon, so stay tuned!</string>
    <string name="str_gift_vip_content">Congratulations, you have become a super VIP user and received a free %1$s from NoiseMedia. You read that right, it\'s free!\nYou can choose to accept or reject, and you cannot revoke this decision after choosing to accept or reject. Please cherish this lucky opportunity.\nIf you choose to accept, then the system will upgrade you for free. After the upgrade, the [Cash pledge] needs to be handled by the user. The NoiseMedia gift is a VIP level, excluding the balance.\n\nPlease choose to confirm the upgrade or reject the upgrade.</string>
    <string name="str_gift_vip_ok">Confirm upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_gift_vip_cancel">Decline upgrade</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_now">Recharge Now</string>
    <string name="str_main_newuser">Your Cash pledge(guarantee fund) is not enough!\nThe balnce must begreater than %1$s. Please recharge! Only when your balance is greater than %2$s can you receive the task of the current level. \n\nWhat does Cash pledge mean? \nIf you upgrade to VIP1 or higher, it means that you have decided to cooperate with NoiseMedia and become a full-time employee, and you must deposit sufficient margin in the balance to maintain the cooperation with NoiseMedia. Of course, this part of the cash pledge can be withdrawn at any time,\nso the cash pledge is only kept in your account balance. After you pay enough deposit according to the current VIP level, members can immediately perform tasks according to their VIP level. Members can withdraw all balances (including all earnings you earn and deposits you make) at any time. When your balance is lower than the cash pledge, you will not be able to receive tasks temporarily\nSome members were upgraded to VIP by mistake, and they do not plan to use the balance as a deposit. Members are advised to invite more friends to earn referral bonus until you earn enough income as cash pledge. If you are not prepared to put your money into your balance as a deposit, then please upgrade with caution as the membership fee will not be refunded to your balance as VIP tiers cannot be downgraded to lower tiers.</string>
    <string name="str_task_number">Number of tasks per day:%1$s\n\nDaily task income:Rs %2$s.</string>
    <string name="str_vip_balance">Price:</string>
    <string name="str_vip_buy">Join now</string>
    <string name="str_vip_effective_date">Effective date:</string>
    <string name="str_team_vip">Your identity: </string>
    <string name="str_team_commission1">Team task income:</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission2">First-level subordinates complete the task and contribute 3% of the task commission to the team leader.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission3">The second-level subordinates complete the task and contribute 2% of the task commission to the team leader.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission4">The third-level subordinates complete the task and contribute 1% of the task commission to the team leader.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission5">Note: VIP0 employees cannot get task commissions.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission6">Upgrade bonus income:</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission7">First-level subordinate employees purchase VIP work qualifications, and reward the team leader with 8% of the actual purchase amount.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission8">Second-level  subordinate employees purchase VIP work qualifications, and reward the team leader with 4% of the actual purchase amount.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission9">Third-level   subordinate employees purchase VIP work qualifications, and reward the team leader with 2% of the actual purchase amount.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission17">Referral bonus income:</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission11">Get Rs 0.5 referral bonus for every friend you invite to sign up through the invite link. This reward is limited to 20 invites.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission12">But you can still get all the upgrade rebates and quest rebates for all the users you invite.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission13">You need to know that the users you invite must meet two conditions:</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission14">1: Register and log in to the Noise Media APP.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission15">2: Complete the tasks on the app.</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission16">A valid invitation is not recognized until the user completes the task.</string>
    <string name="str_my_name">Account</string>
    <string name="str_my_invitation_code">Invitation code</string>
    <string name="str_vip_identity">Your identity</string>
    <string name="str_my_helpbook">Help</string>
    <string name="str_my_customer">Service</string>
    <string name="str_my_fund">Turntable</string>
    <string name="str_my_fund1">Fund</string>
    <string name="str_my_record">Bill</string>
    <string name="str_my_withdrawal">Withdraw</string>
    <string name="str_my_recharge">Recharge</string>
    <string name="str_my_information">Personal</string>
    <string name="str_index_company">Company</string>
    <string name="str_index_profit">Profit Rules</string>
    <string name="str_withdrwal_dailog_title">Bind Usdt</string>
    <string name="str_withdrwal_dailog_content">Please bind the USDT collection address</string>
    <string name="str_withdrwal_dailog_btn">To bind</string>
    <string name="str_bind_usdt_tips">Please enter Wallet address</string>
    <string name="str_bind_usdt_detail1">Tips:</string>
    <string name="str_bind_usdt_detail2">1. NoiseMedia is a global task scheduling system. For the convenience of global employees, we use the unified cryptocurrency USDT trc20 for settlement.</string>
    <string name="str_bind_usdt_detail3">2. Please bind the USDT trc20 address, other addresses will not be able to bind</string>
    <string name="str_bind_usdt_detail4">3. NoiseMedia is a decentralized platform. Each employee account can only be bound to one address and does not support modification. If you bind someone else\'s address by mistake, NoiseMedia cannot modify it.</string>
    <string name="str_index_language">Language</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_method_title">Please select</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_method_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_method_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="str_withdrawal_balance">Available balance</string>
    <string name="str_withdrawal_balance1">Rate</string>
    <string name="str_recharge_help">Recharge help</string>
    <string name="str_index_activity">Activity</string>
    <string name="str_withdrwal_shujijine">Actual amount (%1$s fee)</string>
    <string name="str_addr_0">Please enter your current USDT Address</string>
    <string name="str_addr_1">Please enter your new USDT Address</string>
    <string name="str_addr_2">Re-enter your new USDT Address</string>
    <string name="str_addr_inut_tis">USDT Address are inconsistent, please re-enter</string>
    <string name="str_addr_err">wrong USDT Address</string>
    <string name="str_tixian_addr">Withdrawals USDT Address</string>
    <string name="str_credit_title">Personal credit</string>
    <string name="str_credit_in">Check my credit score</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules">Credit rules</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content1">If the credit score is below 60, the task cannot be accepted</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content2">1. Credit score is dealer management team plan, NoiseMedia does not participate in credit score adjustment</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content3">2. If the credit score is less than 60 points, you will not be able to accept the task</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content4">3. For credit rating issues, please contact the team leader (dealership) directly</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content5">Credit score assessment criteria:</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content6">1: The user must complete the task process completely and realistically (i.e. you do not enter the page where the task must be completed and click the Like button) to ban to skip or cheat</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content7">2: Users should be responsible for the team they invite and keep the whole team active (because if the person you invite does not actually complete the task, it will cause losses for the advertiser). Therefore, we recommend users to have their own After that, create a WhatsApp group of your team and invite NoiseMedia official customer service to enter the group, so that we can better help you activate your team.</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content8">3: The system detects an account with the same IP address on the same device.</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content9">Actions after credit rating reduction</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content10">1: Once the credit score has been lowered by the system, there will be a 15-day evaluation period, during which the system will stop issuing tasks.</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content11">2: You can speed up the credit rating restoration process by inviting new users, and the system will restore your task authority immediately after monitoring team activity.</string>
    <string name="str_credit_rules_content12">3: The credit score of each level is independent. If you cannot receive the VIP1 task after the credit score was judged to be reduced during the VIP1 period, after upgrading the VIP2, the credit score will be reset to 60 points, and you can receive the VIP2 immediately. If you follow the above rules on the new level, the credit score will not be affected.</string>
    <string name="str_rules_title">NoiseMedia Rules</string>
    <string name="str_share_content">I successfully received Rs 1000. You can get it for free when you register. A part-time software that can run on your cell phone. Join my team and earn money happily.</string>
    <string name="str_congratulations_content">Congratulations to %1$s for upgrading to %2$s</string>
    <string name="str_team_commission10">Note:When your subordinates are upgraded to VIP2 or above, you can get the upgrade reward. There is no reward for upgrading to VIP1.</string>
    <string name="str_task_detail">Like it.</string>
    <string name="str_turntable_list">Winner List</string>
    <string name="str_turntable_rules">Successfully invite 1 friend, and you will get 1 raffle.\n\n1.The rewards drawn will be directly deposited into your balance.\n2.The invited user will be considered as having completed the invitation only after completing the task once.</string>
    <string name="str_turntable_count">Remaining raffle times:</string>
    <string name="str_turntable_invite_friends">Invite friends</string>
    <string name="str_turntable_count_err">The number of available times is 0, please invite friends to join to get the number of lucky draws.</string>
    <string name="str_turntable_winning">winning</string>
    <string name="str_withdrawal_sudt_addr">Please enter the USDT collection address</string>
    <string name="str_pay_state_wait">wait payment</string>




    <string name="str_pay_index_det1">Are you satisfied with your poor life?</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det2">Do you want to realize your dream?</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det3">Do you want to get rich but can\'t find a suitable platform?\n</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det4">******************************\n</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det5">We are the game company with the most clicks in India.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det6">The game business is growing substantially every day, and more suppliers are needed to support our work</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det7">The greater the ability, the higher the income\n</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det8">******************************</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det9">We have no scams here, low risk, great income.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det10">We are taking responses if any chargeback comes.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det11">We want you to be positive, sincere and responsible</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det12">Join us!</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det13">******************************</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det14">Requirement:\n</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det15">1. IDFC with Cms</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det16">2. RBL with MQR</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det17">3. HDFC with MQR (old version only)</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det18">4. HDFC CURRENT\n</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det19">Payout:</string>
    <string name="str_pay_index_det20">1. Yesbank with Msme</string>

    <string name="str_pay_usdt_but1">Detail</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_profit">Number of exchanges</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_num">Quantity completed</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_num1">If it is not completed 2 times in a row, it cannot be redeemed within 7 days.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_sell">Sell</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_dialog_submit">Continue</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_dialog_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_dialog_content">1. Please make sure you have enough USDT to trade. \n\n2. If you fail to trade more than 2 times in a row, the account will be banned from trading for 7 days.\n\n3. The recharge address is valid for 30 minutes, please obtain the address Complete the transfer within 30 minutes. If it exceeds 30 minutes, please do not transfer to the expired address to avoid trouble.\n\n4. The recharge will be completed within 1\-5 minutes after you complete the transfer. If you do not receive the money for a long time , please contact online customer service for help.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_home">处理中</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_my">成功</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_3">失败</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_sell_title">Payment USDT</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_number">Sell Quantity</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_get">Get</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_recharge_rules1">Tips</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_recharge_rules2">1. Please make sure you have enough USDT to trade.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_recharge_rules3">2. If the transaction fails more than 2 times in a row, the account will be banned from trading for 7 days.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_recharge_rules4">3. The recharge address is valid for 30 minutes. Please complete the transfer within 30 minutes after obtaining the address. If it exceeds 30 minutes, please do not transfer to the expired address to avoid trouble.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_recharge_rules5">4. The recharge will be completed within 1\-5 minutes after you complete the transfer. If you have not received the money for a long time, please contact the online customer service for help.</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_submit">Pay in USDT</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_number">Account number</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_bankname">Bank name</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_status">Account Status</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_money">Deal today</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_profit">Today\'s Earnings</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_rate">Fee:</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_totalprofit">Total revenue</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_detail">Detail</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_add">Add</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_id">Member ID</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_name">Member name</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_number1">Number of accounts</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_invate_link">Invite link:</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_invate_code">Invitation code:</string>
    <string name="str_pay_mine_copy_link">Copy</string>
    <string name="str_pay_mine_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="str_pay_upload_type">Select Bank</string>
    <string name="str_pay_upload_Radio1">with PM</string>
    <string name="str_pay_upload_Radio2">Self-paid deposit</string>
    <string name="str_pay_member_status1">Pending</string>
    <string name="str_pay_member_status2">Running</string>
    <string name="str_pay_member_status3">Invalid</string>
    <string name="str_pay_member_status4">Stop</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_status1">Pending</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_status2">Success</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_status3">Failure</string>
    <string name="str_no_data1">empty data</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_1">Account No:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_hint_1">Enter beneficiary account</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_2">Holder:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_hint_2">Enter beneficiary name</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_3">IFSC:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_hint_3">Enter Bank IFSC</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_4">Withdraw password:</string>
    <string name="str_extra_ac_hint_4">Enter Withdraw password</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_profit1">Today\'s Earnings</string>
    <string name="str_pay_card_number2">account list</string>
    <string name="str_member_baozhengjin">security deposit:₹ %1$s</string>
    <string name="str_my_balance">Balance(USDT)</string>
    <string name="str_my_interest">≈ INR</string>
    <string name="str_login_send">Send</string>
    <string name="str_tos_login_1">invalid phone number</string>
    <string name="str_pay_usdt_rate">Price</string>

    <string name="str_withdrawal_sudt_addr1">USDT address(TRC20)</string>



    <string name="str_home_deposit">Deposit</string>
    <string name="str_home_content1">Total Value(USDT)</string>
    <string name="str_home_content2">Today Price:</string>
    <string name="str_home_content3">Exchange</string>
    <string name="str_home_content4">WazirX Price</string>
    <string name="str_home_content5">Binance Price</string>
    <string name="str_home_content6">KuCoin Price</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_orderid">Order ID:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_usdt">USDT(TRC20):</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_amount">Rupees:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_rate">Rate:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_accountNo">Account No:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_accountHolder">Account Holder:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_ifsc">IFSC:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_createTime">Create Time:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_transactionTime">Transaction Time:</string>
    <string name="str_order_detail_transactionStatus">Transaction Status:</string>

</resources>